dancehallreggae.com 2016-10-12

# DancehallReggae.com | The King Of Jamaican Dancehall Videos Since 1995

### About DancehallReggae.com

DancehallReggae.com began in 1995 as a regular personal homepage on a college server with emphasis in reggae. Since then the site went through numerous transformations, most of which were due to request from our visitors and has evolved to our current status. With an objective of informing and educating the world about the dancehall and reggae industry, the page also provides premium products and services to our visitors. As a result the site has been in increasing demand and simultaneously we have been adding new features to make DancehallReggae.Com more appealing.

On a weekly basis the HEADLINES is updated with reggae news from around the world. Nevertheless, during the week our DANCEHALL BOARD is always active and other features such as INTERVIEWS, PHOTOS from events and our LYRICS DIRECTORY are updated on a random basis. Also, from our diverse product line we provide dancehall DVDS, SOUND SYSTEM CDs, MIXED CDs, and the latest 7" RECORDS on the market. These pages are constantly updated and furthermore, the site is furnished with a GUESTBOOK for your comments, a HANGOUT with links to other pages and a site tributed to ENTERTAINERS who passed on.

We thank our visitors worldwide for showing their appreciation through our years or toil, past and future advertisers for their support and our contributors for their articles. Even though we may look professional, we are still going through a learning process and your comments and ideas are welcome.

**DancehallReggae.com**  
P.O. Box 1652  
Orange, NJ 07051  
(732) 582-2532  
www.dancehallreggae.com  
support@dancehallreggae.com  

### DancehallReggae.com Privacy Policy

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

* To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
* To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
* To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
* To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
* To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at any time by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.dancehallreggae.com/info/terms-and-conditions

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on 2011/02/22

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.dancehallreggae.com  
Kingston, Jamaica  
support@dancehallreggae.com

### 18 U.S.C. 2257 Record-Keeping Requirements Compliance statement

All actors, actresses, models and other people that appear in all or any visual portrayal of actual sexually explicit conduct appearing or otherwise located within our domain (dancehallreggae.com.com) and subdomains were over the age of eighteen years at the time the videos were made.

All other visual depictions displayed on our websites are exempt from the provision of 18 U.S.C. section 2257 and 28 C.F.R. 75, because they do not portray conduct as specifically listed in 18 U.S.C section 2256 (2) (A) through (D), but are merely depictions of non-sexually explicit nudity, or are depictions of simulated sexual conduct, or are otherwise exempt because the visual depictions were created prior to July 3, 1995.

DancehallReggae.com and its subdomains are not the primary producers (the term is defined in 18 U.S.C. Section 2257) of any of the visual content located in the websites.

Videos and/or Images contained on dancehallreggae.com and its subdomains were published, republished, reproduced or reissued on June 2006.

**DancehallReggae.com**  
P.O. Box 1652  
Orange, NJ 07051  
(732) 582-2532  
www.dancehallreggae.com  
support@dancehallreggae.com
